Anthony Franzosa

Manager/Trainer

Township of Woolwich, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Anthony-Franzosa/eb30ba5746d031c9

A position that will allow me to use my communication skills and experience in the field of pharmacy and training to effectively execute all aspects of the job and efficiently develop structured teamwork using my leadership skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Pharmacist

Fishtown Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA - January 2015 to Present

Responsibilities

- -Practice diversified pharmacy responsibilities with emphasis on customer care and quality assurance, including drug interactions and adverse reactions.
- -Counsel patients and MTM
- -Supervise ancillary staff
- -Handle all telecommunications with health care providers, insurance companies, and patients.
- -Manage inventory
- -Prepare pharmaceutical compounds
- -Analyze Profit and Loss information
- -Multitask and create a highly organized environment
- -Practice medication and dispensing safety
- -Reach goals and expectations by deadlines

Leave of Absence

Home - April 2013 to December 2014

Responsibilities

- -Medical Leave of Absence
- -Primary Care Giver (Stat-at-home Father)

Manager/Trainer

RITE AID PHARMACY - Wilmington, DE - February 2007 to April 2013

Responsibilities

- -Managed a large number of employees in a high volume pharmacy
- -Trained personnel for ancillary, staff and management positions not only in daily skills and goals, but also company protocol.
- -Practiced diversified pharmacy responsibilities with emphasis on customer care and quality assurance, including drug interactions and adverse reactions.
- -Counseled patients and MTM
- -Supervised ancillary staff and staff pharmacists
- -Handled all telecommunications with health care providers, insurance companies, and patients
- -Managed inventory
- -Prepared pharmaceutical compounds
- -Analyzed Profit and Loss information
- -Created a high level of organization with the ability to multitask
- -Medication and dispensing safety

- -Reached assigned goals and expectations by deadlines
- -Scheduled all pharmacy staff
- -Immunized patients

Staff Pharmacist

RITE AID PHARMACY - July 2005 to February 2007

Responsibilities

- -Practiced diversified pharmacy responsibilities with emphasis on customer care and quality assurance, including drug interactions and adverse reactions.
- -Counseled patients and MTM
- -Supervised ancillary staff
- -Handled all telecommunications with health care providers, insurance companies, and patients
- -Managed inventory
- -Prepared pharmaceutical compounds
- -Analyzed Profit and Loss information
- -Created a high level of organization with the ability to multitask
- -Practiced medication and dispensing safety
- -Reached assigned goals and expectations by deadlines

EDUCATION

PharmD

PHILADELPHIA COLLEGE OF PHARMACY - Philadelphia, PA 2005